In this video we will talk
about ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company, the
market cap of the company is
56875 crores,
how much percentage does it give and here you
can see the chart of the company, there is a
discount in the valuation of the company at this time and the
earnings of the company are increasing, that is, there is a
very good opportunity to buy at this time
and if we talk about the positive point in the company, then the
company has reduced its debt and the
company is almost debt free and if we
talk about the percentage and negative point, then the
promoter's holding has reduced by 7.84% in the last 3 years, the
dimension
is 4829 and at this time the share price is 1118 and there is
support of ₹1100 in the market and the
target of the stock is 1300, so if you
want to buy in this company, you
can buy at this time,
if you like the information given in this video, then
like the video, share it
and subscribe to our channel